bloggink.com 2013-06-01

# BlogginK.com Free Blogging Service | Privacy

## Privacy

This privacy policy applies to Google functions on this Web domain. For details,  
visit the [**Google Privacy Center.**](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

## The DART cookie

  * This Web site participates in the Google AdSense® program. We  
sell advertising space to Google for resale to click-through merchants. 
  * Google uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uploads these cookies to your browser. 
  * Google’s DART cookie enables it to target ads to your interests. This  
cookie stores a record of the sites that you visit. This data might determine the  
ad content that you see. 
  * Advertisers can access and use cookies about your visits to this and other Web sites. The  
collected data _doesn’t_ include your phone number, name, address,  
or email address. 
  * Like to know more about this practice? Want to keep companies from using this data? Click [**Your Privacy Choices**](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). A summary appears on this page. 

### Why Google collects data

  * To audit and research, allowing service maintenance and improvements 
  * To protect Google or its users 
  * To provide services, including custom content and advertising 

### What Google collects

  * **Affiliated Google Services.** Google offers services through other Web  
sites. Google might receive personal data that you provide to those sites. Affiliated sites might have their own  
privacy practices. 
  * **Cookies.** When you visit Google, Google sends cookies that uniquely identify your browser. 
  * **Data that you provide.** Registration data (such as your name, email address and password). 
  * **Gadgets.** Google might offer third party applications _(gadgets)._ Under its privacy policy,  
Google processes data that it collects. The provider’s privacy policy  
determines the data that an application or gadget collects. 
  * **Links.** Google might track whether you follow links. 
  * **Location.** Google offers location-enabled services, such as Google Maps for mobile. If you  
use those services, Google might receive data about your location. 
  * **Logs.** When you access Google services, servers record data from your browser. 
  * **User communications.** Google saves email or other communications that you send to Google. 

### Why Google shares personal data

  * Because Google has your consent. 
  * Because the data is aggregate, non-personal data. For example, how many users  
clicked on an advertisement. Such data doesn’t identify you individually. 
  * To process personal data on Google’s behalf. Third parties process such data under Google’s  
privacy policy and other security measures. 
  * To satisfy regulations, enforce terms of service, or manage security problems. 

### Your privacy choices

To serve Web ads, Google uses the DoubleClick advertising  
cookie _(DART)._ For this cookie, you can manage your ad preferences by accessing the Ads Preferences Manager.  
You can opt out of the DoubleClick cookie anytime. To opt out, use DoubleClick’s opt-out cookie.

You can set your browser to show when a site is sending a cookie. You can set your browser to refuse  
all cookies. If you disable your cookies, some Google features might not function  
properly.

You can refuse to submit personal data to any Google service. In that case, Google might not be  
able to provide those services to you.

### Changes to this privacy policy

At the bottom of the page, the revision date identifies the current version.

**Published on: Oct 2, 2010 @ 22:40**

This post is also available in: [French](http://bloggink.com/fr/politique-de-confidentialite/), [Italian](http://bloggink.com/it/privacy-2/), [Spanish](http://bloggink.com/es/su-privacidad/)
